Search

Clear

Search

Search

Clear

Search

Popular Searches

Close Search

toggle mobile menu

In This Section
---------------

Navigation
----------

* Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

Kennewick School District (KSD) is committed to respecting your privacy and protecting any personal information you share with us. You can visit our website without revealing personal information. In some cases , however, we may ask for personal information in order to provide the services you request. Such information will be used by KSD only to conduct official school business and will never be disseminated by KSD to any unaffiliated third party. All of the information that we collect from you is subject to this Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. By using this site, you agree to be bound by these terms.

###   
Terms of Use

This website is intended to provide news and information about KSD. We will make all reasonable efforts to ensure the accuracy and timeliness of content.

No part of this site or its contents - including, but not limited to, the school logo - may be copied, reproduced, modified, retransmitted, distributed, published, commercially exploited or otherwise transferred without written permission from KSD.  

### Information Collection and Use

KSD does not track, collect or distribute personal information about site visitors. However, we do collect some information about site visits. We have access to domain names and I.P. addresses of visitors. We compile statistics that show the number of visitors and the number of requests we receive for particular pages or files on the site. These statistics are used internally to evaluate and improve the site. The statistics contain no personal information (or email addresses) and cannot be used to gather such information.

KSD parents and guardians are provided access to specific password-protected areas of our website, which may contain personally identifiable information, such as contact information for other MCDS parents or families.

###   
Email Privacy and Spam

The website contains email addresses of faculty and staff and (within the password-protected parts of the site) KSD parents and guardians. Use of this information for private, commercial, or political mailings and/or distribution to any outside party is prohibited. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact KSD.

###   
Student Privacy

KSD is committed to protecting the privacy of our students and their families. We may post names and images on the public pages of our website to provide recognition of accomplishments. If a parent or guardian would like to opt-out of their student's name or image being used on the website and other district communication tools, they must fill out the [Release of Student Directory Information](https://www.ksd.org/fs/resource-manager/view/89bc3846-0be7-4207-b508-555ce443cf93).

###   
External Links

This site may contain links to external sites. KSD is not responsible for the privacy policies or content provided by these sites.

###   
Cookies

Using Goggle Analytics we collect some anonymous information about how you use the site by setting and accessing cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small text file containing a unique identification number that is transferred from the web site to your hard drive. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie terminates once you close the browser. A persistent cookie is stored on your hard drive for an extended period of time. The stored cookies will not allow us to learn any personally identifiable information that you have not otherwise disclosed. At no time will the cookies reveal to MCDS or to others your name, email address, street address or telephone number.

The use of cookies is an industry standard, and they are currently used on most major websites. It is possible to adjust your browser preferences to alert you when a cookie is sent to your hard drive, or to refuse cookies altogether. However, this may significantly alter what you are able to see or access on the MCDS website.

To learn more about how Google collects and processes information, go to: [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.google.com%2Fpolicies%2Fprivacy%2Fpartners%2F&data=05%7C02%7Cpatricia.mosley%40ksd.org%7Caaacf30ce131482ca83408dc0013cbe5%7C00948c2509684d128618b9e148ccfe77%7C0%7C0%7C638385332243412852%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&sdata=HQaaF8%2B21UWGlSPEYDLpTCmz1NZsVYPskw1kFMHLw2M%3D&reserved=0 "Original URL: http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. Click or tap if you trust this link.")

KSD’s mission is to provide a safe environment in which every student reaches their highest potential and graduates well prepared for success in post-secondary education work and life.

Find Us

Hours: 7:30 a.m. - 4:30 p.m., Monday-Friday

Administration Center

1000 W. 4th Avenue

Kennewick

WA

99336

(509) 222-5000

Schools

District

Useful Links

Other Links

©2024 Kennewick School District - all rights reserved | [Legal Notices](https://www.ksd.org/fs/pages/7)
